Sewall Wright Papers 1895-1988 Mss.Ms.Coll.60
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1895-1988; 13.5 Linear feet
  - Penrose, L.S., 1949-63 (Box Series I-14)
  - Pereda, Jorge, 1936 (Box Series I-14)
  - Perspectives in Biology and Medicine, 1958-70 (Box Series I-14)
    Ingle, Dwight J.
  - Peters, Helen M., 1941 (Box Series I-14)
  - Peters, James A., 1955 (Box Series I-14)
  - Peters, Joseph J., 1951 (Box Series I-14)
  - Petit, Claudine, 1956-57 (Box Series I-14)
  - Petrunkewitch, Alexander, 1933 (Box Series I-14)
  - Phemister, D[allas] B[urton], 1935 (Box Series I-14)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1960 (Box Series I-14)
    Billman, Carl
  - Philosophy of Science Journa1, 1948 (Box Series I-14)
    Philosophy of Science Association; Churchman, C. West
  - Physiological Zoology, 1945-51 (Box Series I-14)
    Brown, Frank A. Jr.; Allee, W.C.
  - Pickford, Grace E., 1931 (Box Series I-14)
  - Piegorsch, Waiter, 1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - Pincus, Gregory, 1932-40 (Box Series I-20)
  - Pines, A. Leon, 1979 (Box Series I-20)
  - Pirchner, Franz, 1959 (Box Series I-20)
  - Pirie, N.W., 1965-66 (Box Series I-20)
  - Pirlot, P., 1954 (Box Series I-20)
  - Platt, C.S., 1936 (Box Series I-20)
  - Plough, Harold H., 1936-53 (Box Series I-20)
  - Plum, Mogens, 1934-35 (Box Series I-20)
  - Pollak, Edward, 1975 (Box Series I-20)
  - Polnik, Amelia, 1957 (Box Series I-20)
  - Pontecorvo, G., 1946 (Box Series I-20)
  - Pontius, C. B., 1945 (Box Series I-20)
  - Pope, Alton S., 1931 (Box Series I-20)
  - Popenoe, Herbert, 1925 (Box Series I-20)
  - Popenoe, Paul, 1931-54 (Box Series I-20)
  - Popenoe, Wilson, 1931-32 (Box Series I-20)
  - Porter, R.R., 1972 (Box Series I-20)
  - Posner, Stanley I., 1932 (Box Series I-20)
  - Poulson, Donald F., 1944 (Box Series I-20)
  - Powell, Jeffrey R., 1973-77 (Box Series I-20)
  - Powers, John G., 1961 (Box Series I-20)
    Prentice Hall, Inc.
  - Powers, LeRoy, 1936-42 (Box Series I-20)
  - Powsner, Louis, 1934 (Box Series I-20)
  - Preer, John R. Jr., 1948 (Box Series I-20)
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee, 1935 (Box Series I-20)
  - President's Committee on National Medal of Science, 1966-73 (Box Series I-20)
    Crawford, Bryce Jr.; Slichter, Charles P.; Carter, H.E.
  - Preston, F. W., 1951-52 (Box Series I-20)
  - Price, Bronson, 1935-36 (Box Series I-20)
  - Price, David E., 1950 (Box Series I-20)
  - Price, Dorothy, 1959 (Box Series I-20)
  - Price, George R., 1968 (Box Series I-20)
  - Price, Winston H., 1941 (Box Series I-20)
  - Priestly, Herbert, 1957-58 (Box Series I-20)
  - Prigge, Richard, 1936-52 (Box Series I-20)
  - Princeton University Bicentennial, 1946 (Box Series I-20)
  - Princeton University Press, 1950-51 (Box Series I-20)
    Jepsen, Glenn L.
  - Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, 1953-1968; 18 folders (Box Series I-20)
    Drosophila genetics; Lewontin, Richard Charles; National Academy of Sciences; Neel, James V.; Population genetics; Publication -- Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics
    - Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, 1953-62 (Box Series I-20)
      Bailey, Herbert S, Jr.
    - Alexander, Mary D., 1957 (Box Series I-20)
    - Davidson, E., 1953 (Box Series I-20)
    - Edsall, John T., 1968 (Box Series I-20)
    - Forscher, Bernard, 1978-80 (Box Series I-20)
    - Kent, V., 1953 (Box Series I-20)
    - Koehn, Richard V., 1980 (Box Series I-20)
    - Kojima, Ken-ichi, 1968 (Box Series I-20)
    - Last, Jerold A., 1973 (Box Series I-20)
    - Lewontin, Richard C., 1966 (Box Series I-20)
    - MacLane, Saunders, 1966-68 (Box Series I-20)
    - Morton, Newton E., 1978 (Box Series I-20)
    - Neel, James V., 1968 (Box Series I-20)
    - Russell, Elizabeth, 1962 (Box Series I-20)
    - Smithies, Oliver, 1972 (Box Series I-20)
    - Turner, et al., 1975 (Box Series I-20)
    - Williams, Josephine, 1962-66 (Box Series I-20)
    - Wilson, 1953 (Box Series I-20)
  - Prout, Timothy, 1967 (Box Series I-20)
    Nichols, Margaret; Glass, Bentley; Smolker, Rosemary
  - Quarterly Review of Biology, 1947-1967 (Box Series I-20)
  - Quertermus, Carl, 1972 (Box Series I-20)
  - Quijandria, Benjamin, 1970 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rabasa, Sol L., 1951-1963 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rachel, Anna, 1941 (Box Series I-20)
    Metaphase Hatchability Charts
  - Rademacher, Hans, 1940-43 (Box Series I-20)
  - Raffel, Daniel, 1933 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rail, V.A., 1922 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rajasekarasetty, M. R., 1948 (Box Series I-20)
  - Ramsbottom, Ralph, 1933 (Box Series I-20)
  - [Raney], M. L., 1943 (Box Series I-20)
  - Raper, John R., 1954 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rashevsky, Nicholas, 1948-57 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rasmuson, Marianne, 1954 (Box Series I-20)
  - Ratekin, Mayme, 1933-43 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rau, George, 1951-60 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rawles, Mary Elbert (Box Series I-20)
  - Reave, James S., 1950 (Box Series I-20)
    Symposium on Radiation Genetics; The Journal of Cellular and Comparative Physiology; The Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology
  - Rebhun, Lionel L., 1957 (Box Series I-20)
  - Redfield, Alfred C., 1936-1939 (Box Series I-20)
  - Redfield, Robert, 1946 (Box Series I-20)
  - Redwood, Charles W., 1931 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reed, C.I., 1935 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reed, O.E., 1935 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reed, Sheldon C., 1935-51 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reese, H.H., 1935 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reese, William L., 1961 (Box Series I-21)
  - Reeve, Eric, 1950-52 (Box Series I-21)
  - Regnart, Horace J., 1920 (Box Series I-21)
  - Rempel, W.E., 1968 (Box Series I-21)
  - Rendel, James M., 1953-54 (Box Series I-21)
  - Rensch, L.C. Bernard, 1968-75 (Box Series I-21)
  - Revelle, Roger, 1969 (Box Series I-21)
  - Reynolds, Albert E., 1939 (Box Series I-21)
  - Reynolds, Bruce D., 1955 (Box Series I-21)
  - Rhoades, M. M., 1936-46 (Box Series I-21)
  - Rice, V.A., 1934 (Box Series I-21)
  - Rich, Earl R., 1957 (Box Series I-21)
  - Rich, Willis, 1925-47 (Box Series I-21)
  - Richards, Oscar W., 1931 (Box Series I-21)
  - Richardson, E. C., 1935 (Box Series I-21)
  - Richardson, L.R., 1946-47 (Box Series I-21)
  - Richardson, Lewis F., 1950 (Box Series I-21)
  - Richardson, Richard H., 1968-72 (Box Series I-21)
  - Richardson, S[amuel?], 1943 (Box Series I-21)
    Barnes Richardson and Colburn
  - Richardson, T.P., 1921 (Box Series I-21)
  - Richey, F. D., 1931-45 (Box Series I-21)
  - Rick, Charles M., 1943 (Box Series I-21)
  - Richer, W.E., 1947 (Box Series I-21)
  - Ricketts, Henry T., 1963 (Box Series I-21)
  - Rife, D. C., 1953 (Box Series I-21)
  - Riley, Herbert P., 1947 (Box Series I-21)
  - Ristroph, Claire, 1931 (Box Series I-21)
  - Rivkin, Joseph, 1943 (Box Series I-21)
  - Roberts, D. F., 1955 (Box Series I-21)
  - Roberts, Rimer, 1932 (Box Series I-21)
  - Roberts, Harry V., 1950 (Box Series I-21)
  - Roberts, William C., 1947 (Box Series I-21)
  - Robertson, Alan, 1947-80 (Box Series I-21)
  - Robertson, Forbes, 1957 (Box Series I-21)
  - Robertson, W.R.B., 1931 (Box Series I-21)
  - Robinson, Charles E., 1965 (Box Series I-21)
  - Robinson, Dan, 1980 (Box Series I-21)
  - Robinson, H.F., 1961 (Box Series I-21)
  - Robinson, P., 1964 (Box Series I-21)
  - Robinson, Rita Ann, 1950 (Box Series I-21)
  - Robinson, Roy, 1950 (Box Series I-21)
  - The Rockefeller Foundation, 1940-41 (Box Series I-21)
    Hanson, Frank Blair
  - The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, 1931 (Box Series I-21)
    Gowen, John W.
  - Roe, Anne, 1947-70 (Box Series I-21)
  - Rohlf, F. James, 1970 -71 (Box Series I-21)
  - Romer, Alfred S., 1937-39 (Box Series I-21)
  - Roofe, Paul G., 1950 (Box Series I-21)
  - Roscoe B. Jackson Memorial Laboratory, 1948-1961; 7 folders (Box Series I-21)
    Behavioral genetics, IQ; Cancer, chemotherapy; Committee activities; Dunn, Leslie Clarence; Roscoe B. Jackson Memorial Laboratory; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs
    - Canning, Geraldine, 1951 (Box Series I-21)
    - Dunn, L.C., 1950-51 (Box Series I-21)
    - Foley, Dale J., 1954-61 (Box Series I-21)
    - Little, Beatrice, 1950 (Box Series I-21)
    - Little, C.C. (Pete), 1948-50 (Box Series I-21)
    - Scott, J. Paul, 1949 (Box Series I-21)
    - Shaw, Norman, 1948 (Box Series I-21)
  - Ross, Frank A., 1925-31 (Box Series I-21)
    N.V. Martinus Nijhoff Boekhande1
  - Ross, Hans, 1947-48 (Box Series I-21)
    Evans, W.G.; Kaye, I.; Linstead, P.
  - Röth, A., 1935 (Box Series I-21)
    Richey, J. E.
  - The Royal Society, 1963-67 (Box Series I-21)
  - The Royal Society of Edinburgh, 1949-51 (Box Series I-21)
  - Rudnick, Dorothea, 1934-56 (Box Series I-21)
  - Russell, Elizabeth S., 1947-75 (Box Series I-21)
  - Russell, Liane B., 1949-57 (Box Series I-21)
  - Russell, William L., 1940-70 (Box Series I-21)
  - Ruth, Elbert, 1934 (Box Series I-21)
  - Ruth, R.F., 1970 (Box Series I-21)
  - Rutledge, J. J., 1939 (Box Series I-21)
  - Ryan, Francis J., 1962-63 (Box Series I-21)
    XI International Congress of Genetics; Genetics Society of America
  - Ryan, J. M., 1941 (Box Series I-21)
  - Sadler, William S., 1921 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sadusk, Joseph F. Jr., 1949 (Box Series I-22)
    Research and Development Board
  - Sager, Ruth, 1953 (Box Series I-22)
  - St. Victor, Sister Mary B. V. M., 1933 (Box Series I-22)
    Lillie, Frank
  - Salmon, S.C., 1937 (Box Series I-22)
  - Saltis, Douglas, 1949 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sampford, M.R., 1965-68 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sanghvi, L.D., 1951 (Box Series I-22)
  - Santas, Manro, 1980 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sar, Della, 1975 (Box Series I-22)
  - Saunders, A. H., 1933 (Box Series I-22)
  - Savage, L.J., 1949-51 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sawin, Paul B., 1936 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sax, Karl, 1922-47 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sazama, J.J., 1934 (Box Series I-22)
  - Scantlebury, Ronald E., 1952 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schäfer, William, 1936-37 (Box Series I-22)
  - Scheer, B. T., 1957 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schmehl, Francis L., 1953 (Box Series I-22)
    Federal Security Agency-Public Health Service; National Institutes of Health
  - Schmidt, Karl, 1958 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schmidt, Karl P., 1947 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schmitt, Francis O., 1945 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schnell, F.W., 1958-70 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schnetzler, E.E., 1953-54 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schopf, Thomas J.M., 1966 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schrank, A.R., 1968 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schubel, Frank, 1932-48 (Box Series I-22)
    Weldon Memorial Prize; Daniel Giraud Elliot Meda1
  - Schultz, Henry, 1932-35 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schultz, Jack, 1948 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schwab, Joseph Jackson, 1946 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schwartz, Benjamin D., 1977 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schweet, Richard S., 1962 (Box Series I-22)
  - [Schwol, J.], 1934 (Box Series I-22)
  - Science (Box Series I-22)
    - Science, 1962-63 (Box Series I-22)
    - Abelson, Philip H., 1967 (Box Series I-22)
    - Atwood, Mildred, 1947 (Box Series I-22)
    - Bailit, H. L., 1965 (Box Series I-22)
    - Baitsell, George, 1949 (Box Series I-22)
    - Carlson, A.J., 1947 (Box Series I-22)
    - Cattell, Jaques, 1945 (Box Series I-22)
    - Dobzhansky, Theodosius, 1947 (Box Series I-22)
    - DuShane, Graham, 1958-61 (Box Series I-22)
    - Eberhart, Sylvia, 1967 (Box Series I-22)
    - Meyerhoff, Howard A., 1951-52 (Box Series I-22)
    - Moulton, F.R., 1947 (Box Series I-22)
    - Muller, Herman J., 1947 (Box Series I-22)
    - Prout, T., 1961 (Box Series I-22)
    - Thompson, David H., 1947 (Box Series I-22)
  - The Science Press, 1950 (Box Series I-22)
  - Scott, J. Paul, 1935-65 (Box Series I-22)
    Allee, Warder Clyde
  - Scott, George A., 1945 (Box Series I-22)
  - Searle, A. G., 1964-68 (Box Series I-22)
  - Selander, Robert K., 1975-80 (Box Series I-22)
  - Selvin, Hanan C., 1975-76 (Box Series I-22)
  - Senior, J.K., 1934 (Box Series I-22)
  - Serebrovsky, A.S., 1927-32 (Box Series I-22)
  - Serra, J.A., 1945 (Box Series I-22)
  - Seventh International Congress of the International Society for Cell Biology, 1950 (Box Series I-22)
  - Seventh International Congress of Genetics, 1936-1937; 8.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-22)
    Navashin, M.S,; Levit, S.G,; Muller, Herman J.
    Genetics -- Guinea pigs; International Congress of Genetics -- Seventh Congress; Invitations; Levit, Solomon G.; Muller, Hermann Joseph; Navashin, Sergei Gavrilovich; Publication; Russian politics and science; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics
  - Sewell, William H., 1975 (Box Series I-22)
  - Shahin, Karima A., 1979 (Box Series I-22)
  - Shaw, Katharine, 1976 (Box Series I-22)
  - Shay, W.W., 1919 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sheets, E.W., 1925-34 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sheffield, H.A., 1921 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sheppard, P. M., 1960 (Box Series I-22)
  - Shifriss, Oved, 1945 (Box Series I-22)
  - Shine, Ian, 1975-77 (Box Series I-22)
  - Shishmanovitch, Angelina, 1951-54 (Box Series I-22)
  - Shockley, William, 1969-72 (Box Series I-22)
  - Showalter, Hiram M., 1931 (Box Series I-22)
  - Shull, A. Franklin, 1931 (Box Series I-22)
  - Shull, George Harrison, 1922-1934; 2.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-22)
    Conferences and symposia -- Mendel Centennial; Genetics -- Nomenclature; Iltis, Hugo; Publication -- Genetics; Sturtevant, Alfred Henry
  - Siegel, Paul M., 1970 (Box Series I-22)
  - Silberman, David E., 1943 (Box Series I-22)
  - Silvers, Willys K., 1971 (Box Series I-22)
  - Simmonds, N. W., 1952 (Box Series I-22)
  - Simmons, George, 1932 (Box Series I-22)
  - Simmons, George Finlay, 1934 (Box Series I-22)
  - Simmons, L. P., 1948 (Box Series I-22)
  - Simon, Herbert A., 1956 (Box Series I-22)
  - Simpson, George Gaylord, 1945-1947; 5.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-22)
    Conferences and symposia; Evolution; National Research Council -- Committee activities; Population genetics; Publication; Requests for reprints; Reviews
  - Sinauer, Andrew D., 1979 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sing, Charles F., 1969 (Box Series I-22)
  - Singh, Jagmohan, 1948 (Box Series I-22)
  - Singleton, W. Ralph, 1961 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sinnock, Pomeroy, 1969 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sinnott, Edmund W., 1949 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sixth International Congress of Genetics, 1931-1937; 9 folders (Box Series I-23)
    Castle, William Ernest; Demerec, Milislav; Dunn, Leslie Clarence; East, Edward Murray; Genetics -- Guinea pigs; International Congress of Genetics -- Sixth Congress; Little, Clarence Cook; Mouse genetics; Rat genetics; Solicitations for support or contribution; Whiting, Phineas W.
    - Castle, William Ernest, 1931 (Box Series I-23)
    - Demerec, Milislav, 1931-1932 (Box Series I-23)
    - Dunn, Leslie Clarence, 1931 (Box Series I-23)
    - East, Edward Murray, 1931-1932 (Box Series I-23)
    - Hayes, Hebert Kendall, 1931 (Box Series I-23)
    - Ibsen, Heman L., 1931 (Box Series I-23)
    - Little, Clarence Cook, 1931-1937 (Box Series I-23)
    - McPhee, Hugh, 1931-1932 (Box Series I-23)
    - Whiting, Phineas W., 1931 (Box Series I-23)
  - Skala, Virginia L., 1963 (Box Series I-23)
    Mathematics Research Center, United States Army
  - Slater, F.A., 1950 (Box Series I-23)
    Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association
  - Slatkin, Montgomery, 1974-75 (Box Series I-23)
    Cascade Speciation
  - Slatis, Herman, 1951-63 (Box Series I-23)
  - Slaughter, Eileen J., 1950-60 (Box Series I-23)
  - Slye, Maud, 1933-48 (Box Series I-23)
    Harrison, R. Wendell
  - Small, James, 1950 (Box Series I-23)
  - Smith, A.D.B., 1925 (Box Series I-23)
  - Smith, Cedric A.B., 1950-68 (Box Series I-23)
  - Smith, David Clyde, 1956-60 (Box Series I-23)
  - Smith, George F., 1980 (Box Series I-23)
  - Smith, George P., [1974] (Box Series I-23)
  - Smith, Harold, 1935-42 (Box Series I-23)
  - Smith, Harry M., 1951 (Box Series I-23)
  - Smith, J. Russell, 1920 (Box Series I-23)
    Gettys, R.E.
  - Smith, Shelby B., 1960 (Box Series I-23)
    United States Information Agency
  - Smithies, Oliver, 1965 (Box Series I-23)
  - Snedecor, George W., 1960 (Box Series I-23)
    Rau, George J.
  - Snell, George D., 1931-55 (Box Series I-23)
  - Snusted, D. Peter, 1977-78 (Box Series I-23)
  - Snyder, Laurence H., 1931-44 (Box Series I-23)
  - Sober, Herbert A., 1942 (Box Series I-23)
  - Society for Experimental Biology, 1951 (Box Series I-23)
    Brown, R.
  - Society for Mathematical Biology, Inc., 1974 (Box Series I-23)
    Karreman, George
  - Society for the Study of Evolution (Box Series I-23)
    - Society for the Study of Evolution, n.d. (Box Series I-23)
    - Carson, Hampton L., 1950 (Box Series I-23)
    - Clausen, Robert T., 1951 (Box Series I-23)
    - Epling, Carl, 1954 (Box Series I-23)
    - Just, Theodor, 1952 (Box Series I-23)
    - Lewis, Harlan, 1953 (Box Series I-23)
    - Mayr, Ernst, 1946 (Box Series I-23)
    - Patterson, John Thomas, 1947 (Box Series I-23)
    - Stebbins, G. Ledyard, Jr., 1948-49 (Box Series I-23)
  - Society of Systematic Zoology, 1951 (Box Series I-23)
    Blackwelder, Richard E.
  - Sokal, Robert R., 1952-69 (Box Series I-23)
  - Sokoloff, Alec, 1965 (Box Series I-23)
  - Sondhi, K.C., 1970 (Box Series I-23)
  - Sonneborn, Tracy M., 1943-1952; 35.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-23)
    Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- National Academy of Sciences; Cytogenetics; Physiology; Protozoan genetics; Publication -- Genetics; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Southern California Society for Mental Hygiene, 1936 (Box Series I-23)
    Turner, Ethel Louise
  - Sparrow, Arnoia, 1948 (Box Series I-23)
  - Spencer, 1925 (Box Series I-23)
    Sotola
  - Sperry, Charles C., 1933 (Box Series I-23)
  - Spetner, Lee M., 1966 (Box Series I-23)
  - Spiegelman, S., 1945 (Box Series I-23)
  - Spiess, Eliot B., 1961 (Box Series I-23)
  - Spillman, W., 1909 (Box Series I-23)
  - Spiroff, Boris E. N., 1951 (Box Series I-23)
  - Spofford, Janice B., 1956-76 (Box Series I-23)
  - Spuhler, James N., 1956 (Box Series I-23)
    Yearbook of Physical Anthropology
  - Stadler, Lewis John, 1931-1953; 21.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-23)
    Cancer, chemotherapy; Committee activities; Genetics of plants; Lectures, public speaking; Physiology; Radiation genetics; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Stalker, Harrison Dailey, 1939-1964; 4.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-23)
    Drosophila genetics; Neel, James V.; Population genetics; Woodson, Robert E.
  - Staples, John H., 1978 (Box Series I-24)
    W. H. Freeman and Co. Publishers
  - Starr, George Herman, 1953 (Box Series I-24)
  - Starrett, R. H., 1955 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stebbins, C. Ledyard Jr., 1943-49 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stechert-Hafner, Inc., 1950 (Box Series I-24)
  - Steele, Dewey G., 1942 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stein, Kathryn, 1932 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stephens, Stanley George, 1953 (Box Series I-24)
    Slatis, Herman M.
  - Stern, Alfred, 1932 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stern, Curt, 1932-1967; 25.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-24)
    Castle, William Ernest; Conferences and symposia; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Drosophila genetics; Dunn, Leslie Clarence; Fisher, Ronald Aylmer; Genetics -- Cattle; Genetics -- Guinea pigs; Genetics of plants; History of biology, especially genetics; Invitations; Jennings, Herbert Spencer; Mendel, Gregor; Neel, James V.; Population genetics; Publication -- Genetics; Solicitations for support or contribution; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Stern, Kurt
  - Stigler, Stephen M., 1975 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stiles, Karl A., 1953-57 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stockard, Alfred H., 1954 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stockard, Charles R., 1924-34 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stoker, Herman M., 1931 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stone, William S., 1951-55 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stormont, Clyde, 1953 (Box Series I-24)
  - Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station, 1921 (Box Series I-24)
  - Strandskov, Herluf H., 1934-53 (Box Series I-24)
  - Streeter, George L., 1924 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stresisinger, Geroge, 1945 (Box Series I-24)
  - Strong, Leonell C., 1932-52 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stroud, Clyde, 1947-48 (Box Series I-24)
  - Students for a Democratic Society, 1973 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sturtevant, Alfred Henry, 1934-1948; 11.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-24)
    California Institute of Technology -- Thomas Hunt Morgan memorial; Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- National Academy of Sciences; Cytogenetics; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Drosophila genetics; Human genetics -- Race; Invitations; Population genetics; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Sturtevant, Frank M. Jr., 1952 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sturtevant, Mary Evelene, 1935-53 (Box Series I-24)
    Atwood, Sanford S.; Carson, Hampton; Castle, William E.; Hess, Waiter N.; Hull, Fred H.; Jepsen, Glenn; Little, Clarence Cook; Scantlebury, R, E.
  - Sturdy, M.F., 1937 (Box Series I-24)
    Cook, Clarence; Swift, Harold H.
  - Sueoka, Nobory, 1962 (Box Series I-24)
  - Summers, Charles E., 1958 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sumner, Francis B., 1937 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sumption, Lavon, 1956 (Box Series I-24)
  - Suskins, C. Leonard, 1934 (Box Series I-24)
  - Susman, Millard, 1975 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sved, John A., 1968-69 (Box Series I-24)
  - Svihla, Arthur, 1945 (Box Series I-24)
  - Swift, Harold H., 1939-40 (Box Series I-24)
  - Szilard, Leo, 1956 (Box Series I-24)
  - Tabor, Elsie, 1958-78 (Box Series I-24)
  - Tagerelinger, 1922 (Box Series I-24)
  - Talbot, Mary, 1934 (Box Series I-24)
  - Taliaferro, William Hay, 1933-35 (Box Series I-24)
  - Tamarin, Robert H., 1980 (Box Series I-24)
  - Tantawy, Azim 0, 1949-72 (Box Series I-24)
    U.A.R. Genetical Society; Egyptian Journal of Genetics and Cytology
  - Tanzer, R., 1930-31 (Box Series I-24)
  - Targow, Abram Morris, 1934 (Box Series I-24)
  - Tazima, Yataro, 1968 (Box Series I-24)
  - Teissier, Georges, 1935-48 (Box Series I-24)
  - Temin, Howard M., 1971-74 (Box Series I-24)
  - Terrill, Clair Elman, 1951 (Box Series I-24)
  - Theoretical Population Biology, 1969 (Box Series I-24)
    Karlin, S.
  - Thomas, Pamela C., 1966 (Box Series I-24)
  - Thomas, Sannuel Finlex, 1934 (Box Series I-24)
  - Thomas Hunt Morgan Centennial Symposium, 1966 (Box Series I-24)
    Schweet, Richards
  - Thomson, Godfrey, 1940-48 (Box Series I-24)
  - Thompson, David H., 1932-50 (Box Series I-24)
  - Thompson, Paul E., 1943 (Box Series I-24)
  - Thompson, W.R., 1943 (Box Series I-24)
  - Thurow, Gordon R., 1960 (Box Series I-24)
  - Thurstone, Louis Leon, 1947 (Box Series I-24)
  - Timofeeff-Ressovsky, N. W. (Nikolai W.), 1936-1937; 2.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-24)
    Genetics; Population genetics; Publication
  - Tinkle, Donald W., 1962 (Box Series I-24)
  - Tirelli, Mario, 1946 (Box Series I-24)
  - Todd, Horace, 1938-42 (Box Series I-24)
  - Tolman, Ruth S., 1943 (Box Series I-24)
  - Tomkies, J.S., 1927 (Box Series I-24)
  - Torrey, Edward P., 1949 (Box Series I-24)
  - Torrey, Theodore W., 1948 (Box Series I-24)
  - Townsend, J, Ives, 1955 (Box Series I-24)
  - Tsymburskaya, L., 1943 (Box Series I-24)
  - Tuckerman, Louis Bryant, 1925 (Box Series I-24)
  - Tulane University, 1957 (Box Series I-24)
    Penn, George H.
  - Turner, Charles E., 1922 (Box Series I-24)
  - Turner, Helen M., 1955 (Box Series I-24)
  - Turner, John R.G., 1977-79 (Box Series I-25)
  - Twelfth International Congress of Genetics, 1968 (Box Series I-25)
    Tazima, Yataro
  - Twitty, Victor C., 1950-52 (Box Series I-25)
  - Tyler, W. J., 1949 (Box Series I-25)
  - Union of American Biological Sciences, 1931 (Box Series I-25)
    Leighty, C.E.
  - United Kingdom Fulbright Funds (Box Series I-25)
  - United States Committee on Nomenclature for Human Genes, 1946 (Box Series I-25)
    Snyder, Lawrence H.
  - United States Department of Commerce, 1945 (Box Series I-25)
    Civil Aeronautics Authority
  - United States Educational Commission in the U.K., 1949-50 (Box Series I-25)
    Watt, G.; Pifer, Alan; Powell, Monica